JOJO WELSING-JONES

<FRONTEND DEVELOPER/> UX/UI DEVELOPER

SKILLS

UI/UX DESIGN

FRONT-END

RESPONSIVE DESIGN

ILLUSTRATOR/PHOTOSHOP

COMMUNICATION

TECHNOLOGIES

-HTML

-CSS

-JAVASCRIPT

-TAILWIND

-BOOTSTRAP

-REACT

CONTACT

- Email: eruditejones@gmail.com
- ■Instagram: jhay-vine erudite_fx_studios
- LinkedIn: jhay-vine
- Phone: +233 24 138 0253

ABOUT ME

I am a Creative and highly Imaginative individual who is highly enthused with design, aesthetics, problem solving and programming. I like to involve myself with anything that encompasses problem solving and enhancing aesthetics of any design simultaneously.

I have been a front-end developer for over three years now and it I love it because it is one of the rare fields of computing that merges problem solving and aesthetics into a single common discipline.

EDUCATION

2016 - 2020 (KWAME NKRUMAH UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY) Tertiary Education

- COURSE OF STUDY: COMPUTER SCIENCE
- CERTIFICATE: Bsc COMPUTER SCIENCE

2013-2016 (TEMA SECONARY SCHOOL) Secondary Education

- COURSE OF STUDY: SCIENCE
- CERTIFICATE : WASSCE CERTIFIFCATE

EXPERIENCE

2016-2018(FRONT-END DESIGN)

- -Developing front-end designs using HTML for creating basic web structures and CSS for styling all html elements and tags.
- -Creating responsive websites which functions on both desktop and mobile devices.
- -Utilized Javascript to build complex UI and UX Designs
- -Worked and utilized CSS frameworks like SCSS and Bootstrap to speed up development time and meet product deadlines.

2017-2022(UI & UX DESIGN)

- -Mastered design and illustration software like Photoshop, illustrator to creating wireframes and assets for all UI and UX designs.
- -Creating UX, UI and designs in Figma and Adobe XD(Mostly Figma).
- -Creating and implementing prototypes for all User Experiences and User Interfaces for a comprehensive experience for clients before web development commences.

2020-2022(UTILIZING FRONT-END FRAMEWORKS)

- -Studied and used React to build reuseable components to speed up the web development production pipeline.
- -Used React to build fast, easily accessible and bug free websites.
- -Used React to utilize, make fetch requests and connect to backend services for the web project for clients.
- -Used tailwind to build fast and extremlely responsive websites to save time in the styling (CSS)of the web development process.
- -Creating and building Progressive Web Apps.

PROJECTS

- -Created User Interfaces and User Experience Deisgns for Clients.
- -Built and deployed an E-Commerce website.
- -Built and deployed static websites.
- -Built, deployed and eaineered progressive web apps.